什么？
What?
-姐们 管他的 别去了 -我知道 我...
- Girl, fuck that. Just leave. - I know. Like...
我显然不介意付钱
I obviously don't mind paying,
但以这种方式开始约会太奇怪了
but what a weird way to start off a date.
这就是我想说的
That's what I'm sayin'.
你打算以后跟孩子这么说吗？
Is this what you tell your kids?
“我们第一次约会前 真是太浪漫了 孩子们”
"Oh, it was so romantic before our first date, y'all."
“他给我发短信说
"He texted me,
‘提前说一声 这地方只收现金’”
'FYI, this place is cash only.'"
-我已经到了 -姐们...
- I'm already here. - Girl...
我真的很饿
I'm really fuckin' hungry.
我不知道 希望能有一个好结局吧
I don't know. Hopefully, it'll make for a good story.
-晚点打给我 爱你 -好的 我更爱你
- Call me after. Love you. -Okay, I love you more.
-拜 -拜
- Bye. -Bye.
-拜拜 -拜！
- Bye-bye. - Bye!
好了 硬着头皮上吧
Okay, let's do this.
我喜欢辣酱
So I love hot sauce.
我吃什么都要涂辣酱
I literally just put it on every single thing
只要是家里能找到的食物 从披萨到鸡翅
I can find around the house sometimes. From pizza to chicken wings.
即使我会有严重的反酸
Even though it gives me terrible acid reflux.
一直流到我的嗓子眼
It makes its way up to my throat
我觉得马上要吐出来了
and I literally feel like I'm gonna vomit.
-所以... -是啊 那太糟糕了
-So... -Oh, yeah. That, um, sucks.
但我太喜欢辣酱了 所以...
But I love it, so...
-是啊 -是啊
- Yeah. -Yeah.
我喜欢芥末
Like, I love wasabi, but, um,
但墨西哥辣酱对我来说还是太冲了
Mexican spices would be too much for me.
-嗯 我懂 -是啊
-Mmm. Yeah. I get that. -Yeah.
是啊
Yeah.
-怎么了？-我有个疯狂的想法
- What? - I had this crazy thought. I...
我就是觉得我们父母那一代的女人
I just feel like... the women in our parents' generation,
她们更在乎她们的穿着打扮
they just cared more about how they dressed
和她们的外表
and just, kind of, how they looked.
她们更注重女性气质 你明白我的意思吗？
They were more into femininity.
但现在
You know what I mean?
我觉得女生们
Like, nowadays, I feel like girls,
都喜欢穿宽大的衣服 像是罩了个毯子一样
they just wear oversized everything, like it's a blanket.
你懂我的意思吗？你知道我在说什么 对吧？
Do you know what I mean? You know what I'm saying, right?
因为我觉得你穿裙子会很好看
It's like... 'Cause I think you would just look great in a dress.
并不是说你穿毛衣不好看
Not that you don't look good in a sweater,
-但我的意思是 如果你... -还需要什么吗？
-but I mean, if you were... -You guys okay?
没事 我们差不多吃完了 谢谢你
Uh, yeah. Um, pretty much done, actually. Thank you.
好的 剩下的都打包吧
Cool. Yeah, we'll just get this wrapped up then.
-谢谢 -别客气
-Thank you. -You're welcome.
你带现金了吗？
Oh, did you bring cash?
你提醒我了 那...
Yeah. You reminded me, so...
我弟弟要来城里看我了
My brother is coming into town.
如果可以的话 我想带些剩菜回去
If it's cool, I'm just gonna snag these leftovers
-你可以... -好的 没关系
- and, uh, I guess I'll just let you leave... - Cool. No. Yeah.
少付几块钱小费
a couple bucks less on the tip.
这样很公平吧
If that makes sense.
你的围巾浸在面条里了
Your scarf is dipping into the noodles.
可恶！该死！
Oh, fuck! Shit!
我很喜欢这条围巾的 不好意思 服务员
I love this scarf. Um... Excuse me? Excuse me.
快点 过来下 你好 你们有苏打水吗？
Quick, come. Hi, do you have sparkling water?
-苏打水 -有
-Sparkling. -Mmm-hmm. Yeah.
-气泡水 你知道气泡吧？-知道
-Bubble. You know bubbles? -Yeah, yeah, yeah.
再加片柠檬 谢谢
And a lemon, please?
我不知道她是否明白我说的话
I don't know if she understood what I said.
她可能不会说英语
I don't think she speaks English.
今晚很开心
That was, uh, that was fun.
你很可爱
You're really cute.
-谢谢 -真的 我们应该找个时间再约
-Thank you. -Yeah. We should do this again sometime.
-好吧 听着 查德... -嗯
Yeah, look, Chad, um... -Yeah.
我觉得我们不太合适
Oh. I... I don't think we're really a match. You know?
我只是出于礼貌而已
I was literally just being polite.
老实说 你甚至不是我喜欢的类型 所以...
You're not even my type, to be honest, so...
-好的 -很好笑吗？“哈哈 真搞笑”？
-Okay.  -Oh, that's funny? "Ha-ha, it's hilarious"? Yeah.
好吧 祝你找到一个男人 你这个自大的婊子
Okay. Good luck finding a guy, you stuck-up bitch.
什么鬼
What the fuck.
该死
Oh, fuck.
好蠢
Oh. Stupid idiot.
你能不能给他发条短信 就写
Can you please just text him and write,
“你和你的丑围巾去死吧 贱人”
"Fuck you and your ugly-ass scarf, bitch."
我真希望能当场怼回去
Oh, see, I wish I thought of that in the moment.
而不是像个白痴一样站在那里
Instead I just stood there like an idiot.
-我们换一下 -好
-Let's switch. -Yeah.
-我不知道你是怎么做的 莫莉 -做什么？
- I don't know how you do it, Mollie. - Do what?
和别人约会
Dating people.
我最后总是独身一人 对此 我也能接受
And I always end up alone. Which, by the way, I'm very okay with.
诺亚 什么？
No, no. What?
你不需要男人 好吗？或者任何人
You do not need a man, okay? Or anybody, for that matter.
我们就是迪士尼电影看多了
It's just the way we've been raised
对爱情有很多不切实际的幻想
since fuckin' Disney movies.
-是啊 去他妈的爱丽儿 -让她去死
-Yeah. Fuck Ariel. -Fuck her.
蠢女人竟然为了一个男人放弃了整个大海
Stupid bitch left the whole sea for a man.
拜托 去他妈的美女
Come on, now. Like, fuck... Fuck Beauty.
对 去他妈的野兽 我就是野兽
Yeah, fuck the Beast. I am the beast.
你就是野兽！你最棒！
You are the beast! Get it!
时间到了 各位！
Time, everyone!
今天做得很好！我是认真的
Whoo! Great job today, huh? I mean that.
给自己鼓鼓掌
Now give yourselves a round of applause.
干得好！
Great job!
-你很强大！-你很强大！
-You are powerful! -You are powerful!
-看看你这肌肉 -瞧瞧
-Look at how strong you are. -Look at this.
嘿 美女 干吗呢？
没干什么 狗狗很可爱 叫什么名字？
林戈 你现在穿着什么？
该死
Oh, fuck.
你吃过这个吗？
Have you ever had these?
-葡萄？-不 是棉花糖葡萄
- Grapes? - No. Cotton Candy grapes.
吃起来跟棉花糖一样 我没开玩笑
They taste just like them. I'm not kiddin'.
-真的吗？-真的
-Really? -Yeah.
我告诉了我姐姐和我侄女
I told my sister and niece.
她们说:“不可能 去你的”
They were like, "No way, fuck you."
所以我现在顺路买点给她们带过去
So now I'm getting them on my way there.
你侄女跟你说 “去你的”？
Your niece said, "Fuck you"?
是啊 四岁的孩子很难搞
Yeah. Four-year-olds are crazy.
好吧
All right.
我看得出来你不相信我 你必须尝一颗
I can tell you don't believe me, so you're gonna have to try one.
我可不希望你把我当成怪胎
I don't want you leaving here thinking I'm a weirdo.
好吧
Okay.
-我没说错吧？-我的天呀
-Right? -Holy shit.
科学 是啊 科学加油
Science. Yeah. Go science.
你住在附近吗？
Do you live around here?
因为我住在六号过道
'Cause I live on aisle six.
我就是来水果区
I just come to the fruit section
随机搭讪一些站在附近的 长得好看的人
to talk to random, very good-looking people that stand near it.
-这笑话太蹩脚了 -是有点
- That was terrible. - That was kinda terrible.
-很抱歉 -没关系
-I'm so sorry. -It's fine.
-晚安 -你也是
-Have a good night. -Okay. You, too.
你知道吗？管他的
You know what? Fuck it.
反正我已经开了个烂头 索性就豁出去了
I'm already ruining this, so I'm just gonna keep goin'.
你能告诉我你的电话号码吗？
Do you think I could have your number?
这样等我见了我姐姐和我侄女
It's really just so I have a story for my sister
我就有故事可讲了
and my niece when I see them.
因为我们肯定会谈到葡萄
Because I think we're gonna talk about the grapes.
-我只是... -当然
-And I'm just... -Oh, of course. Yeah.
然后我可以告诉她们我遇到了另一个人
Then I can tell them that I met someone else
跟我有同感
who feels the same way.
当然 有道理
Sure. Makes sense, yeah.
好的
Okay.
我们下周可以在这里见面
We can meet here next week
再聊聊西蓝花 如果你愿意的话
to talk about the broccoli if you want.
这主意不错
Sounds good.
-薄雾 -雨林
-Mist. -Rain forest.
-有一点薄雾总是好的 诺亚 -是的 很神秘
- Always good to have a little mist, Noa. -Yes, mystery. Yeah.
我叫史蒂夫
I'm Steve.
-很高兴认识你 -我也是
-It's nice to meet you. -You, too.
我不会给你发短信 虽然我很想发
I'm not gonna text you, but I'll really want to.
-晚安 -晚安
- Good night. - Good night.
-什么？-真的
-What? - Yeah.
-你的电话号码？-对
-Your number? - Yeah.
-在杂货店里？-对
- In a grocery store? - Yeah.
-前天晚上？-对
- The other night? - Yes.
而你今天才告诉我？
And you're just now telling me today?
还以为我们是好闺蜜呢
When you think you had a friend.
不 我只是觉得这很奇怪 你知道吗？
No, I just think it was weird, you know? He was...
-他又可爱又风趣 而且... -是啊
- He was cute and funny and... - Mmm. Okay.
我以为人与人已经不会在现实中相遇了
I didn't think people met people in real life anymore, you know?
他可能已经结婚了
He's probably married.
真是谢谢你了 是啊 他可能已经结婚了
Thank you for that. Yes, he's probably married.
很有可能
Probably.
我已经开始纠结他没有发短信这件事了
Like, I'm already thinking about the fact he hasn't texted.
和女生约会我最爱的事情之一就是发信息
That's one of the things I love about dating women.
少点套路 多些情感依赖 你知道吗？
Less games, more emotional dependence, you know?
所以不要整些有的没的
So don't play the games,
你就做自己就好 管他的
just be you straight out the gate. Fuck it.
也许吧
Maybe.
嘿 你想晚点过来吗？
Hey, do you want to come over later?
我需要一些情感依赖
I could use some emotional dependence.
我的情感依赖可不便宜啊 宝
Well, my emotional dependence ain't cheap, boo.
-嗨 -嘿 你好吗？
-Hi. -Hey! How you doin'?
-很好 谢谢 你呢？-挺好的
-Good, thanks. How are you? -Good. Good.
这个地方真的很不错
This place is really nice.
-是啊 -那些熊...
-Yeah. -The bears are, you know...
恰到好处的肮脏 但很有嬉皮士的风格
Yeah. It's like the perfect amount of, you know, grimy, but hip.
没错
Exactly.
你好
Ayyo.
-你们想好喝点什么了吗？-嗨
-You guys know what you want? -Hi. Um...
我想要一杯曼哈顿和
Can I get a Manhattan with, like,
尽可能多的樱桃 谢谢
as many cherries as you can spare, please?
-樱桃 我喜欢 -我爱樱桃
-Cherries. I like that. -I love cherries.
我要一样的
Yeah. I'll do one more of these, thank you.
收到
Copy.
-给你 -谢谢 -不客气
- Here you go. Here. -Thank you. -You're welcome.
-嗨 -嘿
-Hi. -Hey.
-我叫史蒂夫 -诺亚
-I'm Steve. -Oh. Noa.
好吧 那么 我要问蠢问题了
All right, so, uh... Here come the dumb questions.
你来自哪里？
Where are you from?
-我来自东海岸 -好的
-Um, I'm from the East Coast originally, -yeah. Nice.
你呢？
What about you?
-我来自德克萨斯州 -不错啊
-I'm from Texas. Yeah. -Oh. Cool.
你怎么来这儿了？
What brought you out here?
-我的第二个住院医师实习期 -住院医师
My second residency. -Oh! Residency. -Yeah.
-你是医生吗？-对 我是医生
Are you a doc... A doctor? -I'm a doctor. Yeah.
-对 -真了不起
-Yeah. Yeah. Um... -That's impressive.
我是做再造手术的
I just... I work in reconstructive surgery.
你是指整容
You mean, um, plastic surgery.
-对 就是那个 一回事 -好的
-Yup. That's the one. -Right. -There's only one. -Okay.
-但并不都是隆鼻 -当然了 还有 你知道...
But it's not all nose jobs. No, of course. You got, you know...
-隆胸 -隆胸
-Boob jobs. -Boob jobs.
-提臀 -假体
-You got your butt lifts. -Implants.
-面部提升 -面部提升
-Face-lifts -Face-lifts.
但偶尔我能帮到别人
But you know, once in a while I get to help somebody,
这感觉很好
which is nice though.
前几天有个孩子
There was this kid the other day who came in,
出了车祸 严重烧伤
who had an accident and he was badly burned.
所以这种情况我也会处理
So there's that, too.
-我开玩笑的 抱歉 -谢谢
I was just kidding. Sorry. -There you go. -Thank you.
-你的工作令人钦佩 -没关系
-That is amazing. - Don't worry.
这个量可以吗？
That work for you?
-这么多樱桃可以吗？-是的
-Wow. -That do the trick? -Yes.
-因为我们只有这么多了 -抱歉
-'Cause that's all we got. -I'm sorry. That's...
好极了
Perfect.
我其实是想说多放几颗就够了 谢谢
I only meant, like, a couple. Thank you.
那么 你的家人呢？
So, what about your family?
我没有兄弟姐妹
Well, I, um, I don't have any siblings
我爸爸不久前去世了 所以...
and my dad died a while back, so...
我不确定我妈妈在哪里 因为我们不联系
I'm not sure where my mom is anymore because we don't talk.
-是的 -抱歉
-Yeah. -I'm sorry.
没关系
It's fine. Um...
那你的家人呢？
What about your family?
我父亲在德克萨斯州 我母亲去世了
My dad is in Texas and my mom passed away, actually.
-抱歉 -所以...但是...
-Sorry. -So... But it's...
-抱歉 -没关系
-I'm sorry. -It's okay. It's okay.
好吧 看来我们有一些共同点
Well, we have something in common, I guess.
-是啊 去世的父母 -对
-Yeah, dead parents. -Yeah.
-完美 -好极了
-Perfect. -Great.
我们喝一杯吧
Let's cheers to that.
很协调
coordinated like that.
-你没有照片墙？-没有
-So you don't have Instagram. -Nope.
推特呢？
Wow. What about, um, Twitter?
-绝对没有 -没有？
-Definitely not. -No?
有人在推特上说过什么睿智的话吗？
Does anyone say anything smart on Twitter ever?
-这倒是 -不行 拜托 推特是最差劲的
- That's true. - No way. Come on. It's the worst.
那我现在要怎么跟踪你啊？
I mean, how am I supposed to stalk you now?
你只能亲自上阵了
You're just gonna have to do it in person.
去我家蹲点 传统的方式
You know. Show up at my house, the old-fashioned way.
给我写信
Send me a letter!
-那就再好不过了 -那一定很棒
-That would be nice. -That would be nice.
“敬爱的...”
"Dearest..."
“此致敬礼” 好吧 我会写的
"Yours truly." Okay, I'll do that.
我喜欢 那会让我非常感动
I'd love that. That'd touch my heart.
听上去不错
That sounds nice.
怎么了？
What?
你的笑容很美
No, you just have a nice smile.
-好吧 -是真的
-Okay. -You do.
好了 我们来玩个游戏吧
All right, okay. Let's play a game.
告诉我一些你不想让我知道的事情
Um... Tell me something you don't want me to know.
-这游戏挺有意思 好吧 -是啊
-Hmm... Fun game. Okay. -Yeah.
有风险
Ooh. It's risky.
好的
Yes. Um...
我讨厌约会
I... hate this.
我是说...
I mean, um...
好吧 抱歉
Okay. I'm sorry.
我不是讨厌你 因为你看上去挺不错的
Not you, 'cause you seem cool,
但是...我...
but... No, I...
我讨厌约会这件事
I hate, like, dating.
知道吗？一切与约会相关的都讨厌
You know? Everything about it.
比如尴尬的寒暄
The, like... The awkward preamble.
你问我答之类的
The, like, questions and stuff. The, like...
还有发信息
You know, texting.
-展露最好的一面 -是啊
-The perfect projection. -Yeah.
一切的一切 都让人厌倦
Everything about it. Honestly.
我不知道 我只是觉得
I don't know, I just think that, um...
相信真爱的人都是他妈的白痴
people who, like, believe in true love are fucking idiots.
太蠢了
So dumb.
-真的 -那些人太蠢了
-They are. -They're so dumb.
就像我们把找到幸福的全部希望
Like, we put all our hopes of,
都寄托在另一个人身上
like, finding happiness through someone else.
我只是认为 我也说不好
And I just think that, like,
也许这条路并不适合我
I don't know, maybe it's not meant for me,
因为我已经单身了太久
'cause I've, like, been alone so long,
我习惯了这样的生活
I'm actually pretty good at it.
不管了
Fuck it.
怎么了？
What?
没什么 只是...也许有点操之过急了
No, it's just... Maybe it's a little too much.
有点太快了
A little too fast.
我从未听过男人说出这种话
I don't think I've ever heard a guy say that before.
你要喝点什么吗？或者是吃点什么？
Um, can I, uh... Can I get you something to, like, drink? Or eat?
不用 只要你就够了
No, just... Just you.
-早上好 -早上好
-Morning. -Good morning.
你好
Hello.
-喝咖啡吗？-好啊 谢谢
- Coffee? -Yeah, yeah, please.
-就是为了遮住早晨的口气
Just to, like, hide that morning breath.
天啊 有那么难闻吗？
Oh, God. Is it that bad?
糟糕
Oh, no.
我不会放开你的手
I'm not letting go of your hand.
别闹
Get off. Get off.
我们做爱了
Oh, we had sex.
厉害啊！
Get that D!
两三杯酒下肚后 我心想
Somewhere between the second and the third drink I was like,
“管他的” 感觉特别自由
"Fuck it." And it was actually very freeing.
我的“管他的”建议每次都很有效
My "Fuck it" advice always works. Damn.
我甚至都没有担心我的样子
Like, I wasn't even worrying about how I looked
也没担心我是不是要很久才能高潮
or like, if I was taking too long.
好吧
Okay!
他照片墙账号多少？我要去视奸一下
What's his Instagram? I wanna stalk a little bit.
他不玩照片墙
Oh, he doesn't have one.
-什么？-是真的
-Say what? -Yeah.
什么意思？
Whatcha mean?
不行 这太可疑了
Oh, no, see, that's, that's shady.
抱歉 红色警报
I'm sorry. Red flag.
-好吧 随便了 别给我泼凉水 -拜托了
- Okay. Whatever. Stop raining on my sex parade. - Please?
对了 你还记得保罗吗？
Oh, by the way, um, do you remember Paul?
-保罗？-他是那晚的酒保
-Paul? -He was our bartender.
噢 保罗啊 记得
Oh, yeah. Aw, Paul!
我不记得我们为什么不勾搭了
You know, I don't remember why we stopped hooking up.
他是个好人
He was a good guy.
而且吻技高超
And a good kisser, too.
可能是因为你不肯安定下来
Probably because you can't be tamed.
你是自由的野马
- You need to roam free.
这是真的
That is true.
好了 我得回去工作了 爱你
All right, well, I gotta get back to work. I love you.
-好的 我更爱你 再见 -再见！
-Okay, love you more. Bye! -Bye!
你一定要尝尝这个牛小排 太好吃了
You have to try these short ribs, they're insane.
是啊 看起来很不错
Yeah, they look really good, but I, um...
但是我不吃动物
I just don't eat animals.
但你继续吃吧 别停
But... But keep eating. Don't... Don't stop.
事实上 我希望你把这盘子都吃光
In fact, I actually want you to finish that plate.
我赌你不敢都吃完
I dare you to finish that plate.
-不要 -为什么？
-No! - No, no... Why?
-这是我最爱的... -但它确实...
-This is my favorite... -But it does...
这牛小排...
fucking short ribs.
听着 你必须吃完...
Hey, listen, you have to eat the...
我吃不下了 被你搞得没胃口了
I can't. You've ruined it for me now.
-是啊 -我要去洗个手
- Yeah. - I'm gonna wash my hands, I think.
你有没有告诉任何人关于我的事？
So have you, uh, have you told anyone about me?
也许吧
Maybe.
我告诉我闺蜜莫莉了
My best friend, Mollie.
你怎么跟你闺蜜莫莉说的？
What did you tell your best friend, Mollie?
我说我遇到了一个很棒的男人
Um, that I met a cool guy.
我可能有点喜欢他 就一点点
And I might kind of like him. -Just, like, a little bit. -Uh-huh.
跟我说说莫莉
Tell me more about Mollie.
我们是七年前认识的
Well, we met, like, I think it was like seven years ago,
那时我刚搬过来 我们一起工作了一段时间
um, when I first moved here. We worked together for a bit.
我们很合得来
Think you'd really get along.
我不知道你怎么样 但我吃得很饱
I don't know about you, but I am stuffed.
-我们应该跳舞 -什么？
-I think we should dance. -What?
来吧 来 我们跳舞吧
Let's go. Come on. Yes. Yes, yes, let's go, let's go.
-让我看看你的舞步 -好吧
-I wanna see those moves. -Okay.
让我看看你的舞步 到中间来
I wanna see those moves. Get in the center here.
-我把音乐打开 -来吧
- Let me turn this up. - Here we go.
-好的 -就是左右摇摆一下
- Okay. - Just a little sway.
简单的两步舞
It's just a little two-step for now.
-脚下的小动作才是关键 -主要是表情
-It's all in the little moves. -It's all in the face.
是肩膀
It's in the shoulders.
我会单腿跳
I mean, I can hop.
噢 抖臀 我的天
Oh, the hip thrust! Oh, my God.
这边 那边
This. That.
-对 面向我 -不要 好吧
-Yeah. To me. -Oh, no, no. Okay.
很好
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
看来我们跳上了萨尔萨舞了
Looks like we're salsa-ing.
萨尔萨舞
It's a salsa.
-你...很有一套 -我的天
-You are... moves. -Oh, my God.
我必须得拍下来
I have to. I have to.
抱歉 我真的很抱歉 这是一张非常好的照片
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry. It was a really good picture.
-你必须删掉 -我永远都不会删的
-You need to delete that. -I will never delete that.
我们应该一起去旅行
We should go away somewhere.
你想去吗？
Do you want to?
好啊
Uh, yeah.
-好？-嗯
-Yeah? -Yeah, um...
管他呢 有何不可？
Fuck it. Why not?
-去哪？-去哪都行
-I mean, where? -Wherever.
去个好地方
Somewhere... Somewhere nice.
好玩的地方
Somewhere... fun.
也许会有惊喜
Maybe it'll be a surprise.
-管他的 -是啊
- Fuck it. - Yeah.
是啊
Yeah.
我周末要和史蒂夫一起旅行
Um, I'm going away with Steve for the weekend.
什么？去哪？
What? Where?
-是个惊喜 -等等 诺亚
-It's a surprise. -Hold on, Noa.
惊喜？我不喜欢这主意
Uh-uh. A surprise? I don't like that.
我打算去了 是你说的 “管他的” 还记得吗？
I'm just gonna go for it. You said, "Fuck it," remember?
姐们 你被他迷晕了 我连他本人都没见过呢
Girl, you all dickmatized. I haven't even seen this dude.
该死的 我把这事忘了 稍等
Oh, shit, I totally forgot. Hold on.
我给你发一张他的照片
I'm sending you a picture of him.
他确实挺帅的
I mean, he looks cute,
但我看不清他的正脸 你这个变态
but I can barely even tell, you creep.
他帅得不可思议
Um, he is ridiculously cute.
等我们到了 我给你发信息
I'll, um, I'll text you once we get there
如实跟你汇报一切 好吗？
and let you know everything, okay?
好吧
Okay, fine.
我为你开心
Um, I'm excited for you.
这是直女的梦想成真了 对吧？
It's a straight girl's fantasy come true, right?
-对吧？我爱你 -我更爱你
-Right? -I love you. -I love you more.
-再见 -再见
-Bye. -Bye.
-嘿 -嗨
-Hey. -Hi.
抱歉 今天加班了
Sorry. My day ran long.
听着 我们可能得明早出发
Uh, listen, we're gonna have to leave in the morning.
我查了下交通 简直是噩梦
I just checked the traffic and it's a nightmare.
所以我想不如先去我家
So I figured maybe we go to my place
然后明天一早再走
and then, you know, we leave first thing tomorrow.
-可以吗？-好的
-Is that cool? -Yeah. Okay.
看看你
Look at you.
上车吧 我很开心
All right. I'm excited.
你还好吗？
-How you doing?
-没事吧？-嗯 我没事
-You all right? -Yeah. Good.
该死 我就告诉你吧
Fuck. I'm just gonna tell you.
我们要去卡蒂奇格罗夫 这就是惊喜
We're going to Cottage Grove. That's the surprise.
就是那里
That's it.
-真的吗？-是的
-Really? - Yeah.
-这就是惊喜？-是的
-That's the surprise? -Yeah.
-不是吧 我一直都想去那
What? I've always wanted to go.
-你不是出于礼貌随便说的？
You're not just saying that?
我不是随便说说的 我真的早就想去了
I'm not just saying that. No, I really have.
我讨厌惊喜 所以我很高兴你提前告诉了我
I mean, I hate surprises, so I'm kinda glad you told me.
是啊 我们会玩得很开心的
Yeah, it's gonna be good.
明早去格罗夫！啊！（笑脸）
我的手机没反应了
Ugh. My cell isn't working.
Yeah, the service is, um,
但到了我家信号就好了
shitty, but it's gonna get better at my place.
好吧
Cool.
-空气很新鲜 是吧？-是啊
Fresh air, right? - Yeah.
太不可思议了
It's amazing.
谁能猜到？
Who knew?
有点令人失望
-Kinda disappointing.
在心里评估我吗？
Sizing me up?
-是啊 味道很好闻
Oh. Yeah. Smells good.
这是我姐姐给我的
My sister got me that.
显然她认为我喜欢檀香
Apparently she thinks I like sandalwood.
好的
Okay.
你有无线网络吗？
Do you have, um... Do you have Wi-Fi?
-还是没信号 -该死 肯定是又出故障了
- Still no service. - Fuck, must've gone out again.
对了 我在制作我独家版本的
By the way, um, I'm making my own version
加料古典鸡尾酒
of an old-fashioned with a twist.
里面会放樱桃
And, um, it's gonna have some cherries in it.
真体贴
Very thoughtful.
干杯
Cheers.
-真好喝 -是吗？
That's really good. -Yeah?
尝出什么特殊味道了吗？
Notice any interesting flavors in there?
-桃子？-不是
-Peach? -No.
很接近了
Close, very close.
杏子？
Apricot?
-不是 -不是？
-No. -No?
-什么？又猜错了 -非常接近
-What? Fuck. -So close.
很接近了 再想想
- So close. Come on.
-油桃？-答对了！
-Nectarine? -Yes!
-真的吗？-真的 你答对了
-Really? -Yeah, you got it.
油桃
Nectarine.
你的房子很吓人
Your, uh, your house is intimidating.
你家里都是
You're all, like, you know,
高档鸡尾酒 而我则以外卖为生
fancy cocktails, and I'm like pancakes out of a bag.
是啊 但这就是我喜欢你的地方
Yeah, but that's what I like about you.
不做作
No pretending.
对了 我在卡蒂奇格罗夫订的房间
By the way, that, um... The house in Cottage Grove,
有热水浴缸
it has a hot tub.
我不知道你的那个大包里装了什么
I don't know what you packed in that big bag of yours,
但是可调花洒 多灯光模式 应有尽有
but adjustable jets, multiple lights, the whole ordeal.
那里会像过年一样
It's gonna be like New Year's Eve in there.
抱歉 你说什么？
What? Sorry.
你需要一件泳衣
You're gonna need a bathing suit.
诺亚 看着我
Noa. Noa, look at me.
你为什么坐这么远？
Why are you sitting so far away?
过来
Come here.
该死
《绝命邀约》
-嘿 -嗨
Hey. Hi.
你睡得好吗？
How did you sleep?
很好
Yeah, good. Um...
怎么回事？
What... What happened?
我给你下药了
I drugged you.
我在哪？
What, um...
怎么回事 史蒂夫？
What's going on, Steve?
我会告诉你 但你肯定会吓坏的
I'm gonna tell you, but you're gonna freak out.
不
No, no. No, no, no, no.
-史蒂夫 把锁链解开好吗？
Steve, can you take these off, please?
-不行
Can't do that.
你能给我解开吗？
Can you take these off?
-不行 -史蒂夫
-Can't do that. -Steve.
给我解开
Take this off.
不行
I can't do that.
不
No. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
不 不 不
No, no, no, no, no. No. No.
-不 这不是真的 -这是真的
-No. No. This isn't happening. -Yeah, it's happening.
这不是真的
This isn't happening. This isn't happening.
这是真的
Yes, it is.
求你了 你是在跟我开玩笑
Please, please, please, please. This is a joke.
对吗 史蒂夫？
Isn't it, Steve?
-听着 你何不试着...
Look, why don't you just try to...
-诺亚 -别过来
-Noa. -Don't! Don't! Don't!
-我就待在这儿 -别靠近我
-I'm gonna stay right here. -Don't come near me.
-别靠近我 -我哪都不去
-Do not come near me. -I'm staying right here.
史蒂夫
Steve!
诺亚
Noa.
拜托 诺亚 动动脑子 怎么...
Come on, Noa, think. What...
我的天啊
Oh, my God. Oh, my God!
史蒂夫
Steve...
你要强奸我吗？
are you gonna rape me?
我不会强奸你
I'm not gonna rape you.
我喜欢你 诺亚 我喜欢你
I like you, Noa. I like you.
好吗？现在
All right? Now,
我希望你 非常仔细地听我说 好吗？
I want you to listen to me very carefully, okay?
你在听我说吗？诺亚！
Are you listening to me? - Noa!
很好
There you are.
我现在要告诉你
I'm gonna tell you now.
我要把你的肉卖掉
I'm gonna sell your meat.
有人花大价钱买 还有你的头发
People pay me a lot of money for it. And your hair.
还有身体的其他部分
And weird shit like that.
这是一些人的癖好 所以
It's a thing. So...
我不会杀你...
I'm not... I'm not gonna kill you...
不会立刻杀掉你
uh, right away...
因为肉越新鲜越好
Because the fresher the meat, the better.
所以我会尽可能地让你活着
So I'm gonna keep you alive for as long as I can.
除非你主动求死 好吗？
Unless you act up.
但是听好 在那之前 我会好好照顾你的
All right? But listen, until then, I'm gonna take care of you.
我会给你做饭
I'm gonna cook for you.
我其实厨艺很棒 你还没见识过
I'm actually a really good cook. You don't know it yet.
只要你乖乖的
As long as you don't act up,
不会有什么不好的事情发生 好吗？
nothing bad has to happen, all right?
而且你瞧 这里也没那么糟嘛 对吧？
And look. This isn't bad, right?
看看这日落多美
By the way, look at the sunset. Look...
嘿
Hey, hey, hey, hey...
-过来 -不
-Come here. Come here. -No! No! No!
没事了
It's okay. It's okay. It's okay. It's okay. It's okay.
不
No! No!
安静点 冷静
Be quiet. Calm down.
别这么激动
Stop being so dramatic.
没事了
It's okay. It's okay.
好了
There you go.
嗨 你在哪？
Hi, where the fuck are you?
你害我担心死了
You're getting me all freaked out.
给我打电话或发信息
Call me or text me.
我想知道他带你去哪了
And I wanna hear where he took you.
我们在卡蒂奇格罗夫！我晚点打给你 这里信号不太好
虚惊一场
Trippin'.
救命！
Help me!
他不在这儿
He's not here.
救命 救救我 求你了 我什么都愿意做
Help me! Help me, please! Please! Please, I'll do anything!
我帮不了你 我们同病相怜
I can't... I can't help you. We're in the same boat.
该死
Fuck!
告诉我你的名字
Tell me your name.
诺亚
Noa.
我叫佩妮
I'm Penny.
我是来镇上旅游的
I was in town visiting.
遇见了史蒂夫
Met Steve.
我现在正慢慢地被吃掉
Now I'm slowly... being eaten.
-你来这里多久了？-我记不清了
How long have you been here? I've lost track.
我甚至不知道现在是什么时间
I'm not even sure what time of day it is, to be honest.
肯定有人在找你
People have to be looking for you.
你的朋友 家人 警察
Your friends, your family, the police.
肯定有人在到处找你呢
People have to be searching by now.
问题是 我没有什么家人
The problem is, I don't have much family.
我也是
Me neither.
这就说得通了
Makes sense.
还有其他人吗？
Are there others?
除了我们之外 还有一个
Just one other besides us, I think.
嘿 梅丽莎 你能听到我说话吗？
Hey, Melissa, can you hear me?
她已经疯了
She's lost her mind.
但我能理解
But I get it.
不怪她
No judgment here.
我们得离开这里
We have to get out of here.
史蒂夫 医生 波特兰
史蒂夫 整形外科医生 波特兰
还好吗？再多给我发点照片！
该死的...
Motherfucking...
我玩得很开心！
不过需要来个“科技”断舍离 所以我要暂时关机了
好吧
Okay.
真的假的？好吧...爱你！
想体验一次荒野逃生吗？
我靠
Fuck.
给我打电话 有急事！
梅丽莎·邓顿
梅丽莎
你好吗？
Hey. How are you?
还在生气
Still angry.
-至少尝尝蛋糕 -我需要洗个澡
-At least try the cake. -I need to shower.
一个人洗？
Alone?
开个玩笑 这是个愚蠢的玩笑
It's a joke. It was a stupid joke.
我在努力 知道吗？
I'm trying, you know? I'm trying to...
我在努力逗你笑 但不起作用
I'm trying to make you laugh and it's not working.
你就不能对我笑一下吗？拜托 就一下
Can't you just give me one smile, please? Just one?
你是同意了吗？
Is that a yes?
好吧
Okay.
老天 你得放松一点
God, I mean, you're gonna have to loosen up a little bit.
我知道情况有些不同 但还是我啊 对吧？
I know things are a little different, but it's still me, you know?
还是那晚在酒吧的那个男人
Still the guy I was at the bar that night.
我对你说的一切都是真心的
I meant everything I said to you.
没有套路 对吧？没有完美假象？
Just... no games, right? No projections?
这不是你想要的吗？
Isn't that what you wanted?
你会乖乖的吗？
Are you gonna be good?
坏女孩
Bad girl.
-我动不了 -我知道
- I can't move. - I know.
我给你打了麻醉 所以你不会有多少痛感
I gave you an epidural, so you won't feel much.
你在做什么？
What are you doing?
我要切掉你的屁股
I'm taking your ass.
不
No.
-是的 -不
-Yes. -No.
你失去了我的信任 诺亚
You lost my trust, Noa.
所以你要承担后果
So there are gonna have to be consequences.
求你了
Please.
我在灼烧你的屁股
I'm cauterizing your ass
这样就不会弄得到处都是血了
so you won't be a bloody mess.
-求你住手 -诺亚 不会有事的
- Please stop. -Noa, it's gonna be okay.
我是医生 记得吗？
Hey, I'm a doctor, remember?
嘿
Hey.
唷 谢谢你让我顺路过来
Yo. Thanks for letting me stop by.
我也没得选啊 所以...
Yeah, well, you didn't really give me a choice, so...
老天 别装作一副不想见到我的表情
Boy, stop acting like you didn't wanna see me.
我想再次看到你的脸
And I wanted to see your face again.
-你想看我的脸？-是的
-You wanted to see my face? -Yeah.
-你想看我的脸 -确实
You wanted to see my face. - I did.
莫莉 你真是一点都没变
Mollie, you ain't never gonna change.
我还是不能给你他的信息
I still can't give you his info.
就算我有的话
If I even had it.
拜托 求你了 这是我现在仅有的线索了
Come on, please? It's the only connection that I have right now.
你为什么不报警？
Why don't you just go to the police?
-报警？-对
-The police. -Yeah.
跟警察说什么？我最好的朋友跟一个男人走了
And say what? That my best friend went away with a guy
并延长了行程 她给我发信息
and extended her trip and she's texting me,
但我觉得不是她本人发的？
but I don't think it's her?
为什么不行？她是白人 对吧？
Why not? She white, right?
别这样
Don't do that.
不 我开玩笑的 听着 我明白
No, I'm playin', I'm playin'. Listen, I get it.
我明白 但我可能会失去工作 莫莉
I get it. But I could lose my job, Mollie.
听着 她不会一声不响地就消失的 好吗？
Look, she wouldn't just disappear like this, okay?
-我可以告诉你他们什么时候来的 -莫莉
- Look, I can tell you when they were here. - Mollie.
她说当时是你的班
She told me that you were their bartender
他肯定用了信用卡 对吧？
and he must have used a credit card, right?
哪怕只是告诉我他的姓氏 也是帮了我大忙
Look, even just his last name would be a huge help.
求你了
Please?
你在做什么？
What are you doing?
她在噘嘴 不要噘嘴 别这样
She's doing the pouty lip. Don't do the pouty lip. Don't do that.
-考虑一下吧 就当是为了我？-我会考虑的
- Just think about it. For me? - I'll think about it.
-能握个手吗？-你还记得？
-Can we shake on it? -You remember that?
-你记得吗？-你问我...该死
-Do you remember it? -Do I... Shit.
-嘿 -走吧
-Hey. -Get outta here.
-顺便说一句 你状态不错 -我？
- You lookin' good, by the way. - Me?
是因为胡子
It's the beard.
现在连一起了
Yeah, it's connecting now.
我用了新胡须油
Got this new beard oil.
诺亚 你的屁股怎么样？
Noa. How's your ass?
还是没了
Still gone.
止痛药让我没那么痛苦
The pain meds are helping me not care as much.
他真是体贴啊 是吧？
He's so sweet, right?
我想报复 佩妮
I just wanna hurt him, Penny.
我满脑子想的都是这个
It's all I think about.
真不敢相信我和他睡了
I can't believe I slept with him.
等等 你跟他睡了？
Wait, you fucked him?
我从来没有过
I never did.
其他人都没有
I don't think any of the others did either.
我不是在荡妇羞辱你
I am not slut-shaming you, by the way.
我这么说是在夸奖你
I'd say it's a compliment.
我真是太蠢了
I'm so fucking stupid.
不 你不蠢
No. You're not.
这不是我们的错 诺亚
It is not our fault, Noa.
这是他们的错
It's... always... theirs.
布兰登·史蒂夫·坎普 我被你的噘嘴打败了...
安·坎普
什么...
What...
搞什么？
The fuck?
别碰我
Get the fuck off me.
该死的
Fuck.
-你做到了 -妈妈 我成功了
-Wow, you did it. -Mom, I made it!
我找到了他家 他有一个完整的家庭
不是吧！你打算怎么做？
《搞定男人的十种方法》
第十条 多微笑 相信我们！
多加樱桃 这是你应得的
- Extra cherries. You've earned it.
可恶
Oh, fuck.
我好累
I'm so tired.
凌晨2点醒来 一晚都在想
Woke up at 2:00 a.m. last night going,
“不是吧？凌晨了？”
"Really? Now?"
我必须6点起床 我不能接着睡了
I had to be up at 6:00. Then you know you're not going back to sleep.
再过三小时就他妈得起床了 药物有用吗？
You're up fuckin' three hours later. How are the meds?
好极了 还是不愿意面对现实？
Great, great, great. Still in denial?
好吧...
Yeah. Well...
听着 这会花上一点时间
Look, it's gonna take a little time,
但最终你会学会接受
but eventually, you're gonna learn to accept
事情并不总是跟你预想中一样
that things don't always turn out the way you thought they would.
我们都会死
You know, we all die.
但重要的是 我们打算如何面对死亡
But it's really just how we decide to go out.
你为什么要跟我睡 史蒂夫？
Why did you sleep with me, Steve?
我告诉过你
I told you, I, um...
我告诉过你 我喜欢你
I told you, I liked you.
不管怎样 那是一个错误
Anyway, it was a mistake.
好了 试着放松一下
All right, try to relax.
恐惧和压力会影响肉质
Fear and stress isn't good for the meat.
如果你读到这里 意味着他喜欢你 好好利用
继续战斗 不要放弃 -萨米·阿克巴里
佩妮？
Penny?
佩妮 求你了 回答我
Penny, please, just answer already.
求你了 佩妮
Please, Penny.
-佩妮 -什么事？
- Penny! - What do you want?
该死
Oh, fuck.
老天啊
Jesus.
回应我有那么难吗？
Now, was that so hard?
我完了 诺亚
I'm done, Noa.
不 你没有
No, you're not.
我都不知道自己是谁了
I don't even know who I am anymore.
我希望他吃饭呛到
I hope he fucking chokes.
然后他感染了绦虫
And then he gets a fucking tapeworm.
从里面把他慢慢吃掉
And it just eats him from the inside, slowly.
还有他那些变态的朋友
And that all his weirdo friends
屎和呕吐物从眼睛里流出来
shit and puke out of their eyes
直到最后全部死去
till they all fucking die.
你真是个好姑娘 佩妮
You're such a sweetheart, Penny.
只是...
Just...
坚强点
stay strong.
好吗？
Okay?
莫莉想分享她的位置
以防万一计划失败 或者 你可以稍后来找我
不管你卖什么 我都不感兴趣
Whatever you're selling, I'm not interested.
不是 我不是推销的 抱歉
Oh, no. I'm not selling anything. Sorry.
-我叫莫莉... -我认识你吗？
My name is Mollie, and... Do I know you?
不认识
No.
我正在寻找我的朋友诺亚
But I'm looking for my friend, Noa,
我希望你能帮助我
and I was hoping you could help me.
我想你丈夫可能认识她
I think your husband might know her.
只耽误你一分钟
It really should only take a minute.
你知道这听起来有多奇怪 对吧？
You do realize how strange that sounds, right?
我知道
Yes, I do, and, um...
而且我真的不知道该怎么说
I don't really know how to say this, but, um...
但我想她可能在跟你丈夫约会
I think she may have been seeing your husband.
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
嗨
Hi.
-您需要什么吗？-不用了 谢谢
Do you need anything? - No. Thank you.
好吧
Okay.
人肉是什么味道？
What does it taste like?
那取决于是哪里的肉 以及如何烹调
It depends on where it comes from and how it's prepared.
但是...
But...
如果处理得当
if it's done right...
那就是人间美味
it's fucking exquisite.
是你从未体验过的极致口感
It's like nothing you've ever had before.
就这样？
That's it?
我要做晚饭了 去游戏室玩一会 好吗？
Go up to the playroom while I make dinner, okay?
太好了 我先到的
Yeah! I got here first!
听着
Listen, um...
我不确定照片里的男人就是我丈夫
I'm not even positive that's my husband in the picture.
你看不到他的正脸
You can't really see the face.
而且 今早他上班前我还见过他 所以...
Plus I saw him this morning before he went to work, so...
-给你 -谢谢
-Here. -Thanks.
老实说 这件事太疯狂了
Honestly, this is... This is crazy.
既然你这么担心你朋友 你应该报警
You should go to the police if you're so worried about your friend.
他以前有没有出城
Does he ever go out of town
-工作过？-没有
-for work or anything? -No.
他们一周前去了卡蒂奇格罗夫
Well, they went away to Cottage Grove, like, a week ago,
从那以后我就再也没有她的消息了 我只是...
and I haven't heard from her since then and I'm just...
我不知道那在哪里
I don't know where that is.
-我只是很担心 好吗？-我明白
-I'm just worried, okay? -Yeah, I understand.
我真的很抱歉
I'm really sorry.
我丈夫回来了 你得走了
That's my husband right now. You need to leave, okay?
我只是走投无路了 咱们女人之间说一句
I'm just desperate. Woman-to-woman,
也许你丈夫知道更多信息
maybe your husband has more information.
我不是来找事的
I'm not trying to mess anything up for anybody here.
-嗨 -我只是想找到我的朋友
I'm just trying to find my friend.
-你好 嗨 -嘿
-Hello. Hi. -Hey.
-这是怎么回事？-没什么
-What's going on? -Nothing.
没什么 这个女人正要走
Nothing. This woman was just leaving.
-你是史蒂夫 对吧？-不 我是布兰登
- You're Steve, right? - No, I'm Brendan.
但别人都叫你史蒂夫 对吧？
But you go by Steve, right?
不是 就是布兰登 你是谁？
No. Just Brendan. Who are you?
我是莫莉
I'm Mollie. Um...
我的朋友诺亚 我想你认识她 她失踪了
My friend Noa, uh, I think you know her, she's missing.
诺亚 抱歉 我不认识
Noa. Um... No, I'm sorry, I... I don't.
-你认识吗 亲爱的？-当然不认识
-Do you, honey? -No, of course not.
太可怕了 我不知道 我想你找错房子了
That's terrible. Yeah, I don't know, I think you have the wrong house.
是啊 你也许是对的
Yeah. Yeah, you're probably right.
-好吧 抱歉打扰了 -没事
-Okay. -I'm sorry. Sorry about that. -No.
很遗憾我们帮不上忙
We're sorry we couldn't help you.
我们很同情你朋友的遭遇
Sorry about your friend.
你最后一次见她是什么时候？
I'm just thinking, when's the last time you saw her?
诺亚
是你
Oh, it's you.
莫莉 对吧？
Mollie, right?
你真不该多此一举
Really shouldn't have done that.
发生了什么事？
诺亚说我们会合得来
Noa said we'd get along.
该死的
Fuck!
让我们检验下
Let's see.
你为什么问我人肉的味道？
So... why did you ask me what it tasted like?
我不知道
I don't know.
我想我只是好奇
I guess I was... curious.
你好奇？
You were curious?
你觉得我会相信吗？
You expect me to believe that?
信不信随你
You can believe what you want.
好吧
Okay.
我们一起吃晚饭 看看你有多好奇
Let's have dinner and we'll see how curious you are.
我给你带来了一些衣服
Brought you some stuff.
我猜你可能想换个打扮
Figured you might wanna... change.
拜托 你在哪？
莫莉的位置
该死
Fuck.
孩子们都睡了吗？
The boys go down okay?
他们要找你
They asked for you.
-工作怎么样？-挺好
How was work? -Good.
明天我会晚点回来
Actually, I'm gonna be late tomorrow night.
因为新产品的关系 有很多工作要做
Lots to do now with the new product.
一些大客户等着收货呢
Got some big clients expecting deliveries.
-我要洗个澡 -今天合作愉快
- I'm gonna take a shower. -Good teamwork today.
姓名:约翰逊 日期:4月1日
姓名:阮 日期:1月20日
放心 我不会给你下药的 不会干第二次
Don't worry, I'm not gonna drug you. Again.
你最好不要
You better not.
干杯
Cheers.
你之前提到你很好奇
So you mentioned you were curious.
-对 -好吧 你想知道什么？
-Yeah. -All right, what do you wanna know?
嗯...
Well... Um...
你第一次尝试是什么时候？
When did you first try it?
我当时18或19岁
I was, um, 18 or 19.
19岁 对 而且你看
Nineteen, yeah. And, look...
这不是我一时兴起
it wasn't an overnight thing, you know?
一开始我真的很害怕
First, I was actually horrified.
我怎么能做出这种事？
I mean, how could possibly be capable of doing something like this?
我是个正常孩子 我有朋友 过着正常的生活
You know, I was a normal kid, I had friends, I had a normal life,
现在我得面对这些
and now I gotta deal with this thing
我无法与任何人分享
that I couldn't share with anybody.
这让我饱受煎熬 但我总是忍不住去想
And that killed me. But I couldn't stop thinking about it.
我无法舍弃对人肉的迷恋
I couldn't get the, um, taste out of my mouth.
那种质感
The texture.
我很喜欢 我喜欢那种唇齿间的滋味
I liked it. I liked the way it made me feel.
所以我想
So I thought,
“我必须找出 是否还有更多跟我一样的人”
"I gotta find out if there's more out there," you know.
“我不可能是唯一有这种癖好的人”
"I can't possibly be the only person that feels this way."
事实证明 我确实不是
And I wasn't.
有一整群人都沉迷于此
There's a whole community of people that are devoted to this.
就在那一刻 我的人生开始变得有意义
And that's when my life started making sense.
我是说 那是一个非常强大的组织
I mean, it's... It's a very powerful thing.
这整个世界 如果你知道的话
This whole world, if you only knew. It's, um...
生命的意义在于奉献
It's about giving.
把自己交给别人
Giving yourself over to somebody.
永远与他人合而为一
Becoming one with somebody else, forever.
那是非常美妙的事
And that's... That's a beautiful thing.
那是臣服
That's surrender.
那是爱
That's love.
这个组织里有多少人？
And how many people are in this community?
不多
Not many.
最富有的1%人群中的1%
The one percent of the one percent.
没有什么是这些人买不起的 对吧？
You know, there's nothing these people can't afford, right?
他们想要的是别人没有的
They want the one thing that no one else has
或者得不到的
or can get.
我填补了这个空白
And that's where I come in.
我可以给他们供货
I can get it for them.
我因此在圈子里出了名
I made a name for myself.
你们只吃女人吗？
Is it only women that you eat?
-对 -为什么？
-Yeah. -Why?
这是市场的需求 另外 女人的味道更好
That's where the market is. Plus, women just taste better.
所以...
So...
我准备了一道菜肴
I cooked us something.
如果你愿意尝试的话
If you're open to trying it.
这是...
Is it...
这是我的肉吗？
Is it me?
不是
No.
我们一起吃
We'll have a bite together.
这顿饭价值三万美元
This meal is about $30,000.
-太疯狂了 -如果她还活着 价格更高
-That's crazy. -Be a lot more if she was still alive.
希望
Hope.
那是她的名字
That was her name.
有点好笑
Kinda funny.
是有点好笑 太蠢了
It's kinda funny. Stupid.
跟我想象中不太一样
It's not what I expected.
这味道
It's, um...
难以形容
It's indescribable.
-谢谢你 史蒂夫 -不客气 诺亚
-Thank you, Steve. -You're welcome, Noa.
你知道我怎么晓得你很特别吗？
You know how I knew you were special?
因为你跟我一样都不正常
'Cause you're fucked up, too.
我们走吧
All right. Let's go.
诺亚
Noa!
佩妮 是你吗？
Penny. Yeah?
肯定不是梅丽莎
That definitely didn't sound like Melissa.
是啊 听起来像新人
Yeah. Sounds like someone new.
前几天晚上
You know, the other night,
我在想 跟你聊天
I was thinking about how nice
有多开心
it's been to talk to you.
但后来我想 有没有可能你不是真的
But then I was like, what if you're not real...
莫莉的位置不可用
是我自己疯了？
and I'm just going crazy?
像梅丽莎那样
Like Melissa.
但我想如果自己有一个想象中的朋友
But I feel like if I had an imaginary friend,
我不会给她起名叫诺亚
I wouldn't name her Noa.
我会叫她肖恩·康纳利
It'd be, like... Sean Connery.
真希望能见到你
I wish I could see you.
我也是
Me, too.
我有东西给你
I have something for you.
来吧 打开它
Go ahead. Open it.
你喜欢吗？
Do you like it?
是粉色的
It's pink.
我很喜欢
I love it.
谢谢
Thank you.
也许你可以今晚穿上
Maybe you can wear it tonight and,
我们可以再次一起吃晚饭
we can have dinner again.
好啊
Yeah. Okay.
我7点来接你
I'll pick you up at 7:00.
-我对时间已经没有概念了 -我知道
-I have no idea what time it is. -I know.
当然
Sure.
也许你可以梳洗打扮一下
Maybe you can freshen up.
安 你什么时候回家？
你好 嗨
Well, hello. Hi.
看来我们已经进展到正经约会了
I see we've made it to the dinner table.
是的
Yes, we have.
这是约会吗 史蒂夫？
Is, um...? Is this a date, Steve?
也许是吧
Maybe it is.
嗯...好吧
Well... All right.
这将是一个有趣的夜晚
It's gonna be an interesting night.
-是啊 确实 -好极了
- Yeah. It is. - Great.
让我们大醉一场
Let's get drunk.
我在想你那天晚上说的话
I was thinking about what you said that night.
关于独自长大
About growing up alone and all.
让我意识到没有人真正为你做过饭
Made me realize nobody's ever really cooked for you.
这让我很难过
And that made me sad.
每个人都必须有人为他们做一次饭
Everyone has to have someone cook for them once.
肉酱
Pate.
-肝脏 -还有大蒜和迷迭香
- Liver. - And garlic and rosemary.
我确实吃出了大蒜的味道
I do taste the garlic. Definitely.
你可以下次做 以你喜欢的方式
You can make it next time. Just the way you like it.
这是谁？
Who's this?
这个？
This?
这是梅丽莎
This is Melissa.
梅丽莎
Melissa.
这名字太普通了 不是吗？
I mean, that's so boring. Isn't it?
就好像她...
Like, she...
她的肉尝起来有滋有味 而她竟然叫梅丽莎
She tastes so, you know, decadent... and her name's Melissa.
好吧...
Well...
我以为你会说“愉悦”
Thought you were gonna say something, you know, like, Joy.
-看来希望都被吃光了 -没有 希望还剩下很多
- Guess we finished all of Hope. - Oh, no, there's more Hope left.
梅丽莎享受过烛光晚餐吗？
Did Melissa ever get a candlelit dinner?
欢迎来到我的世界
Welcome to my world.
客户想要与女性更亲密
The clients wanna feel closer to the women.
她们以某种方式成为你的一部分
They become a part of you in some way.
这是梅丽莎
There's Melissa.
答案是没有 她从来没吃过烛光晚餐
And no, she never had a candlelight dinner.
佩妮·吉文斯
我的物品在哪里？
Where is my stuff?
在我这里
With me, I guess.
好了 走吧 还有很多美味等待品尝
All right, come on. There's more to eat.
我们一直没去成卡蒂奇格罗夫 对吧？
We never did make it to Cottage Grove, did we?
太可惜了
That's too bad.
那里真的很宁静
It's really serene out there.
让我想拥抱一棵树
Really makes me wanna hug a tree.
总之 谁知道呢？也许我们还可以去
Anyway, who knows? Maybe we could still go.
好的 所以这是胸口肉
Okay, so this is, uh, breast meat.
真的很好吃
And it's, um, it's really nice.
油脂丰富 口感滑嫩
It's fatty and subtle.
甚至有种熟悉的味道
I don't know. It might even be familiar.
-怎么了 ？-不 这是... -这难道是...
-What? -No, it's... -Is it...?
不 这是...
No, it's, uh...
太傻了
It's just stupid.
-没事 说吧 -我说不出口
-No, no, no, go ahead. -No, I can't.
说嘛 你得告诉我
Come on. You gotta tell me.
没什么 就是...
No, it's just, um...
好胸不怕晚
You saved the breast till last.
-我的天啊 -这笑话...很好笑
- Oh, my God. - That was, um... That's good.
这顿饭真丰盛 史蒂夫 你知道吗？
This is really nice, Steve. You know?
你是对的 从来没有人为我做饭 所以...
You're right, no one has ever cooked for me, so...
这跟我预想中的约会不太一样 但是挺不错的
It's not quite how I pictured it, but, you know, it's... It is nice.
-是啊 -她的胸部比我的好看
- Yeah. - She's got better tits than me.
你没有不同意见吗？
You're not disagreeing?
-不 不是... -谢谢 史蒂夫
- No, it's not... -Thanks, Steve.
-我不是那个意思 -谢谢你了 史蒂夫
-I wasn't saying that. -Thanks a lot, Steve.
怎么...
What's...?
抱歉 我只是...
Sorry. Sorry, it's just...
我只是...
Um, it's just...
太美好了
It is really nice.
我脑子很乱
It's... all just so confusing.
我没办法消化
And I can't quite process...
因为我觉得很难受
'cause I feel awful.
我觉得很难受
I feel... awful.
因为我一点都不觉得内疚
'Cause I don't... I don't feel awful.
-该死的 -嘿 过来
-Fuck. -Hey, come here.
诺亚
Noa.
嘿
Hey.
没事了
It's okay.
一切都会好起来的
It's all gonna be okay.
你只是跟别人不一样
You're just different.
从遇见你的那一刻起 我就知道了
And I knew it from the moment I met you.
我忘了给你戴上手铐
I forgot to handcuff you.
是
Yeah.
你忘了
You did.
你想跳舞吗？
Do you wanna dance?
好啊
Yeah.
我想
Yeah, I do.
该死的！
Fuck!
牙膏
你这贱人！
You fuck!
我的天啊！
Oh, God!
快点
Come on, come on.
你这个该死的婊子
You fucking bitch.
快啊
Hurry.
该死的 诺亚！
Goddamn it, Noa!
你这个该死的婊子！我要把你的心挖出来！
You fucking bitch! I'm gonna cut your heart out!
我的天 莫莉 你还好吗？
Oh, my God, Mollie. Are you okay? Are you okay?
我很抱歉 嘿 过来 好了
I'm so sorry. Hey, come on, come on. Okay.
-该死 -把手给我
-Oh, fuck. -Give me your hand.
-你的嘴怎么了？-我以后再告诉你
-What is wrong with you? -I can't tell you right now, but I will.
-把鞋穿上 我马上回来！-你要去哪里？
- Put those on. I'll be right back! - Where are you going?
佩妮？天哪 佩妮 你还好吗？
Penny? Oh, my God, Penny! Are you okay?
终于见到你真是太好了 你还好吗？莫莉！
It's so good to finally see you. Are you okay? Mollie! Mollie!
-诺亚？-莫莉 过来帮忙！
-Noa? -Mollie, come help!
-诺亚？我的天啊 -快点 我们得走了
-Noa? Oh, my God. -Come on, we gotta go.
-你还好吗？-是的
-Are you okay? -Mmm-hmm. Yes.
你还行吗？
You good?
可恶
Oh, shit!
该死的
Oh, fuck.
莫莉
Mollie. Mollie.
Mollie.
-过来 -不！
-Come here. -No. No!
你要去哪 诺亚？你要去哪？
Where do you think you're going, Noa, huh?
你以为你能逃走吗？
Where do you think you're going? Think you're going somewhere?
你哪都去不了
You're not gonna fucking leave.
去死吧
Fuck.
我们得离开这里
We gotta get the fuck outta here.
该死的
Fuck.
老兄 这地方真他妈令人毛骨悚然
Naw, son, this shit is creepy as fuck.
我一定是走错了方向
I must've taken a wrong turn back there.
太诡异了
This some bullshit.
拜托 莫莉
Come on, Mollie.
你在哪？
Where you at?
他怎么把你也抓起来了？
How the fuck did he get you?
我当时在找你 结果找到了他
I was trying to find you, but I found him.
我就知道事情不对劲
I knew shit was off.
对不起 是我连累了你
I'm so sorry. It's all my fault.
你们两个太可爱了
You guys are so cute.
可恶
Oh, fuck! Oh, shit.
-你没事吧？-我没事
-Are you okay? -Yeah, I'm okay.
快起来 我扶你起来
We gotta get up. I'm gonna pick you up.
诺亚！
Noa!
该死的
Oh, fuck.
那家伙追上来了
Oh, this fucking guy!
该死
Fuck.
诺亚！
Noa!
你骗了我
You lied to me!
我要杀了你们这些该死的婊子
I'm gonna kill all you fucking bitches!
小心 他有枪
Watch out! He has a gun!
我得撤了
Naw, fuck this shit.
我们得分开 之字形前进
We gotta split up. We gotta zigzag.
可恶
Fuck.
拜托 电影里都是这么演的
Come on, man, we seen this movie.
要是再不走 就得死在这儿了
We don't make it out this bitch alive, you know this.
GPS定位出问题了
GPS got me twisted and shit.
诺亚！
Noa!
我很抱歉
I'm sorry!
好吗？我很抱歉
Okay? I'm sorry!
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
你想让我说这个吗？
Is that what you want me to say?
拿个手电筒来
Get a flashlight.
安
安 未接电话
去吧 你就继续躲起来 你他妈一直躲着！
Go ahead, you keep on fucking hiding. You keep on fucking hiding!
愚蠢的
Stupid fucking weak
软弱的臭婊子
pussy-ass fucking bitches.
那就是你们 臭婊子
That's what you are. Fucking bitches.
出来
Come on!
该死的
Fuck.
嘿 你个没屌的混蛋
Hey, you fucking half-dick!
死猪
Pig!
来呀 给我笑一个
Come on. Give me a smile.
该死的
Fuck.
我们做到了 好吗？我们安全了
We did it, okay? We're safe.
佩妮 你没事吧？
Penny, are you okay?
该死的
Fuck!
没有信号
I don't have any signal.
可恶 我把手机落那了
Oh, shit. I left my phone.
-好吧 你跟佩妮待在一起 -什么？
-Okay, you stay with Penny. -What?
-你要回去吗？-我得拿我的电话
-You goin' back out there? -I gotta get my phone.
-听着 一定要回来 好吗？-好
-Look, come right the fuck back, okay? -Okay.
-我说真的 -我会的
-For real. -I will.
过来
Come here.
-我们得清理一下 -是 女士
- We need to clean this up. - Yes, ma'am.
-把他的尸体放到冰块上 -是 女士
- Let's get his body on ice. -Yes, ma'am.
快点
Come on, come on.
找到了
Yes. Yes.
-我的天 你杀了他 -什么？
-Oh, my God, you got him. -What?
我以为这永远不会结束 你杀了他
I thought this would never end. You got him.
-你是谁？-谢谢你 我们现在自由了 对吧？
-Who are you? -Thank you. We're free now, right?
-什么？-谢谢你
-What? -Thank you. Thank you.
-有信号吗？-没有
- Anything? - Nothing.
该死的
Oh, fuck.
那是什么？
What the hell is that?
我要看着你断气
I wanna watch your life slip away.
你个贱人！
You fucking cunt!
莫莉！
Mollie! Mollie!
你这个肮脏的荡妇
我当初求过你帮忙
I asked you for help!
都是因为有你这种贱人 我们才活得那么艰难
Bitches like you are the fucking problem!
她到底是谁？
Who the... Who the hell is that?
史蒂夫的妻子
Steve's wife.
什么？
What?
他结婚了？
He's married?
生前结过婚
Was... Was married.
-我他妈爱死你了 莫莉 -我更爱你
-I fucking love you, Mollie. -I love you more.
（也许:查德）在吗？